What you don't see will kill you.
Wrong Turn 3: Left for Dead is a horror, thriller
film directed by Declan O'Brien.
A group of people find themselves trapped in the backwoods of West Virginia, fighting for
their lives against a group of vicious and horribly disfigured inbred cannibals.
Nate, played by Tom Frederic.
Alex, played by Janet Montgomery.
Sophie, played by Louise Cliffe.
Trey, played by Jack Gordon.
Deputy Ally Lane, played by Emma Clifford.
U.S. Marshall, played by Todd Jensen.
Wrong Turn 3: Left for Dead is a 2009  slasher film directed by Declan O'Brien, written by
Connor James Delaney, and starring Tom Frederic, Janet Montgomery, and Tamer Hassan.
An international co-production between Summit Entertainment from the United States and Constantin Film from Germany, it is a sequel to Wrong Turn 2: Dead End (2007) and the third installment in the Wrong Turn film
series, it follows a group of convicts' transfer bus crashes in the West Virginia woods, as they and a corrections officer encounter a young woman fleeing cannibalistic hillbillies who murdered her friends.
Wrong Turn 3: Left for Dead was released on October 20,
2009, by 20th Century Fox Home Entertainment.
The film was panned by critics, and had grossed $5.9 million in home sales.
It was followed by a prequel, Wrong Turn 4: Bloody Beginnings (2011).
The film explores themes of sheriff, river, penitentiary, forest, west virginia.
The tone is dark and intense.